Sex. Murder. Blackmail. There's a first time for everything.
Mini's First Time is a comedy, crime, drama film directed by Nick Guthe.
Desperate to be free from her drunken, unloving mother Diane, the beautiful, scheming young Mini seduces her
stepfather Martin and soon convinces him to join her in a sadistic scheme to have Diane declared insane.
But their conspiracy soon escalates to murder and when John Garson, a young detective
starts investigating, Martin and Mini begin to turn on each other.
Martin Tennan, played by Alec Baldwin.
Minerva 'Mini' Droggs, played by Nikki Reed.
Mike Rudell, played by Jeff Goldblum.
Det. Dwight Garson, played by Luke Wilson.
Jimmy, played by Joe Egender.
Diane Droggs Tennan, played by Carrie-Anne Moss.
Mini's First Time is a 2006 satiric neo-noir black comedy film written and
directed by Nick Guthe and produced by Trigger Street Productions.
It was screened at the Tribeca Film Festival on May 1, 2006,
and had a limited release on July 14, 2006.
It was released on DVD on October 24, 2006 by HBO Films.
The film explores themes of lolita, blackmail, dark
comedy, stepdaughter, escort service.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.